Eddie Andersson

Web developer



Personal information

F-mail: eddandersson@gmail.com

Phone: 0732534406

Address: Stora Essingen, 11265

Stockholm

34 Age: Driving Yes

license:

in 🖸 Links:

Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React.js

Typescript

Git

Node.js

SQL

PHP

Wordpress

Woocommerce

Next.js

Angular

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Languages

Engelska: Avancerad Svenska: Modersmål

About me

I'm a full-stack web developer located in Stockholm, Sweden. I'm finishing my two-year Higher Vocational Education program as a web developer with a focus on e-commerce in May of this year. Since October 2022, I've been doing my internship as a front-end developer at Stryda (formerly G-Loot), where I've learned a lot about working with real projects and best practices. I have a background in service professions such as waiter and furniture salesman, but since obtaining my bachelor's degree in business economics in 2017, I have worked more with administrative economics. I'm a curious person who loves to learn new things, solve complex problems, be creative, and feel like I'm really developing. I would define myself as humble, focused, social, and a problemsolver.

Portfolio

https://eddiewebdev.herokuapp.com

Education

Web development with a focus on e-commerce

Medieinstitutet | 2021 - 2023

This is a full-stack web developer education where I've learned things such as how to work with databases, build and integrate APIs, build responsive websites, version control, and work agile. The education includes both frontend and backend with a focus on e-commerce.

Courses (total 400 YH-points):

Completed:

- E- and M-commerce 10p
- Competence portfolio and entrepreneurship 10p
- Frontend 160p
- Work and project methodology 15p
- System development framework 30p
- Development towards e-commerce platforms 30p
- Database technology 20p
- System support and integration with 3rd party systems 30p
- System development 50p
- Internship 150p
- Thesis 30p

Ongoing:

• Internship 275p

Business administration bachelor's degree

Stockholms Universitet | 2014 - 2017

Focus: Finance

Bachelor's thesis: "Monday Effect at the Swedish Stock Market"
A study on how seasonal effects affect the Swedish stock market.

Natural Science

Östra Reals gymnasium | 2004 - 2007

Work experience

Frontend internship full time

Stryda | 2022-10-10 - ongoing

As an intern at Stryda (formerly G-Loot), I work in a team of developers with different tasks, such as updating and improving the admin interface, creating new features for the website, and solving general bugs and issues. Every day, I work with tools such as React.js, TypeScript, Tailwind, Git, Jira, and Slack. In my team of developers, we have an agile way of working. We have a daily stand-up, backlog refinements, and daily contact with other departments of the company to ensure our solutions work and to know what our next priority is.

Board member and treasurer

Brf Strykugnen 4 | 2021 - ongoing

Economist and Salesman

Mio Försäljning AB | 2014 - ongoing

My work at Mio includes selling furniture, handling administrative economics, keeping in contact with suppliers, banks, and other partners. I also conduct internal training regarding sales, exports, furniture, and the business system Movex.

Waiter

Restaurang Croque | 2013 - 2014

Waiter

Snaps bar och bistro | 2010 - 2012

References

Mustafa Hamra, Engineering Manager

Stryda

Mustafa@stryda.gg

Harris Dailianis, Engineering Manager & Frontend developer

Stryda

Harris@stryda.gg

Lars Andersson, Education manager

Medieinstitutet

lasse@medieinstitutet.se

Sophia Ackås, Store manager

Mio Försäljning AB

Contact information is given on request

Rigmor Hansèn, Store manager

Mio Försäljning AB Contact information is given on request